Now that you've had a little introduction to the theory behind k-fold
‫بعد أن سمعتم مقدمة بسيطة ‫عن النظرية التي يقوم عليها التحقق المقطعي بطريقة k-fold،
cross validation,
‫فقد لا تتفاجؤون إذا عرفتم أننا
it might not surprise you to know that we're going to take a look at the code.
‫سنلقي نظرة على ‫التعليمة البرمجية الخاصة به.
K-fold cross validation is supported in the cross validation
‫&rlm;تدعم مجموعة الدالات ‫الخاصة بالتحقق المقطعي المتاحة
set of functions that are available in sklearn.
‫في sklearn التحقق المقطعي ‫بطريقة K-Fold.
So I want to show you what it looks like when it's being deployed.
‫وأريد أن أعرض لكم كيف يبدو ‫عند نشره.
The code that I have right here is code that you're actually
‫التعليمة البرمجية الموجودة هنا ‫هي تعليمة برمجية تعرفونها جيدًا
already familiar with.
‫بالفعل.
This is the code that we used in the very first mini project,
‫فهذه هي التعليمة البرمجية التي استخدمناها ‫في المشروع الصغير الأول،
to identify the author of the emails.
‫لتحديد كاتب رسائل البريد الإلكتروني.
Was it Sara, or is it Chris?
‫هل كانت سارة أم كان كريس؟
I'm just using a Gaussian Naive Bayes.
‫فأنا أستخدم خوارزمية مصنِّف بايز المبسط الغاوسي فحسب.
I'm keeping track of the training time, the predicting time and
‫وأتابع وقت التدريب، ‫ووقت التنبؤ
the accuracy that I get for this classifier.
‫والدقة التي أحصل عليها بالنسبة ‫لهذا المصنف.
Remember, the features that I am using are the words in the emails and
‫تذكروا، أن الميزات التي أستخدمها ‫هي الكلمات الموجودة في رسائل البريد الإلكتروني
I'm trying to predict who wrote the email based on the vocabulary that's
‫وأحاول التنبؤ بكاتب ‫رسالة البريد الإلكتروني وفقًا للمفردات
being used.
‫المستخدمة.
Up above that I see some feature transforms that I'm doing,
‫وهنا أعلاها أرى بعض عمليات تحويل الميزات ‫التي أجريها،
I am reading in the text, and I'm doing some feature selection.
‫حيث أقوم بالقراءة من النص ‫واختيار الميزات.
These are all things that we've talked about,
‫جميع هذه الأمور ‫تحدثنا عنها من قبل،
so I won't belabor them too much right now.
‫لذا لن أطيل الحديث عنها ‫كثيرًا الآن.
More interesting bit of code is up here.
‫الجزء المثير أكثر للاهتمام من التعليمة البرمجية هو الجزء الموجود هنا.
The first thing that I do is from sklearn.cross_validation I import KFold,
‫أول ما أقوم به هو استيراد ‫KFold من sklearn.cross_validation
which is the name of their k-fold cross-validation function.
‫وهو اسم ‫دالة التحقق المقطعي بطريقة k-fold لديهم.
Then I have to declare a k-fold object, which accepts two arguments.
‫وبعد ذلك علي إعلان كائن k-fold، ‫والذي يقبل وسيطتين.
One is the number of items in the total data set.
‫إحداهما هي عدد العناصر ‫الموجودة في مجموعة البيانات بأكملها.
So in this case,
‫في هذه الحالة،
I say that's the same as the number of authors in the data set.
‫أقول إنه هو عدد الكتاب نفسه ‫الموجود في مجموعة البيانات.
And the second argument is going to be how many folds do I want to look at.
‫والوسيطة الثانية ستكون ‫عدد الحقول التي أريد البحث فيها.
In this case, the answer is two.
‫في هذه الحالة، ستكون الإجابة حقلين.
This is something that you might want to change though.
‫مع ذلك، هذا أمر قد ترغبون ‫في تغييره.
So then what k-fold is going to do is it's going to give me two lists.
‫إذن ما سيقوم به k-fold هو ‫أنه سيعطيني قائمتين.
The first one is going to be a set of indices of
‫ستكون القائمة الأولى ‫عبارة عن مجموعة من الفهارس
all the data points that I'm going to use in my training set.
‫تضم جميع نقاط البيانات التي ‫سأستخدمها في مجموعة التدريب الخاصة بي.
The second list is going to be a list of all of the indices that I'll use in my
‫أما القائمة الثانية فستكون عبارة عن قائمة ‫بجميع الفهارس التي سأستخدمها في
test data set.
‫مجموعة بيانات الاختبار.
then what I can do is I can use these indices to go into my features and
‫ومن ثم، فما يمكنني القيام به هو استخدام ‫هذه الفهارس للبحث في الميزات
into my labels and to assign each set of features or each label,
‫والتسميات وتعيين ‫كل مجموعة من الميزات أو كل تسمية،
to either my training or my testing data set.
‫إلى مجموعة بيانات التدريب أو ‫مجموعة بيانات الاختبار.
So this is the actual partitioning of the data into the training and
‫إذن هذا هو التقسيم ‫الفعلي للبيانات إلى
testing data sets.
‫مجموعة بيانات التدريب ومجموعة بيانات الاختبار.
Then, below that it's just like before,
‫وأسفل ذلك، فالأمر مماثل لما قمنا به من قبل،
we do a little bit of transformation on our training and our testing data.
‫حيث سنقوم ببعض عمليات التحويل ‫في بيانات التدريب والاختبار.
Then we train our classifier and we assess the accuracy.
‫ثم نقوم بتدريب المصنف ‫وتقييم الدقة.
Now if I just do this out of the box,
‫ولكن إذا قمنا بذلك مباشرةً،
something kind of wrong is going to happen.
‫فسيحدث ‫خطأ ما.
So let me show you what happens when I run this code.
‫دعوني أعرض لكم ما ‫يحدث عندما أقوم بتشغيل هذه التعليمة البرمجية.